

## MUHAMMAD MUBEEN

Product Design | UI/UX Designer | Graphic Designer

☐ Email: mu-mubeen@outlook.com

■ Phone: +92 342 3510876

Dribbble: mu\_mubeen

Website: www.theuxfixer.com

Location: lahore, Pakistan

### About me

Hey I'm a Senior UI/UX Designer with great of experience in understanding and designing digital products from concept ideas to production. I work with my clients to help them create web apps and mobile apps from the ground up or to help them solve business problems through visual and usability improvements.

## Education

**BS-Information Technology** 

Bahauddin Zakariya University, Multan (2015 – 2019) CGPA-3.0/4.0

### **Skills**

Adobe Creative Suite **FIGMA** sketch CorelDRAW Balsamiq Invision **Usability Testing** User Experience (UX) Logo Sketching Prototyping Wireframing **UX** Research Mobile App Design Website Design Mobile App Design Saas App User Interface Design **Designing for Print** Calligraph Sketching Branding & Identity **User-centered Design** Visual Design **Image Retouching** Teamwork CSS **JavaScript** HTML

## **Work Experience**

Total 6+ years

#### **Lead Product Designer at Techverx**

Apr 2023 · Presen

I join the company as a product designer, I am working on two key products: the Point of Sale (POS) system whose name is Friday and the Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) software. My role involves collaborating with cross-functional teams to design user-friendly interfaces, workflows, and data visualization tools that provide seamless experiences and real-time insights for both products.

#### Senior UI/UX Designer at Citrok

Feb 2022 · Mar 2023

I joined Citrok as a Senior UI/UX Designer, My responsibility is product design and different service like CMS, SAAS, Mobile apps, and websites Some of the Product names are People Data Labs, ADSS and Usearch.

# UX Designer at Thinkdone solutions

May 2020 - Jan 2022

My position in the TDS was as a UX designer, I did many projects like the Elevatyx, and the Kelger Management was designed and developed also. I have also done E-commerce products whose names are the DrGlow website, MFC(Myfastcoaching) App, and KFC(Keto fast coaching) App.

## UI/UX & Graphic Designer at Xaavia Studios

Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

I joined XaaviaStudio as a UI/UX Designer. I designed a professional branding suite for one of their clients mentioned Blackstone including the logo, Website design, Marketing material, and App design as well. I also designed the entire product of the Text Neck App launched by Moltyfoam.

#### Visual Designer at Bee's Buzz

Aug 2019 - July 2018

At Bee's Buzz, I specialized in social media, branding, and printing for clients like Qadir Burger, Dolphine Adventure Club, Kebabolus, Fine Pizza, Dr. Faisal Azeem, Dr. Maryam, and Rosi, enhancing their recognition and success.

#### Graphic Designer at Aura Communication

Oct 2017 - Jun 2018

At Aura Communication, I've worked on various projects for Mughal Steel, Big Bird, Cake and Bakes, and Marhaba Foods. My responsibilities included social media management, printing, and branding, all aimed at boosting their success and visibility.